<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Glympse – Review</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Glympse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Folders</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/folders/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;By default when you upload a file, they will be in the root of the review table. This may be preferable when there are one or two files uploaded, but once you start to get more and more files uploaded, you may want to organise the files into subdirectories or folders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To add a folder click the New Folder button and enter a name for the folder.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_new_folder.png&#34; alt=&#34;New folder&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_new_folder_name.png&#34; alt=&#34;New folder&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be added to the Home page, you can drag files into this folder, alternatively, if you enter a folder and then click upload, it will upload the file directly to this folder.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_folder_added.png&#34; alt=&#34;New folder&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you drag a file into a folder, the row of the folder you have selected will be highlighted green, release the file and it wil be added to this folder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively you can use the menu for each folder or item to move files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click the dropdown menu button for the file or menu you wish to move and select Move.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/move_files.png&#34; alt=&#34;Move Files&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
This will bring a folder tree where you can click on the folder you wish to move the files to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/move_file_modal.png&#34; alt=&#34;Move Files&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click save changes and the file(s) will be moved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the dropdown menu you can also rename files/folders as well as move them to the bin. Files in the bin will permanently deleted after 30 days.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share File</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/share_file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/share_file/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;It is posible to share the review file to anyone who is in the production group by simply copying the link from the browser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to share a link with someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t have access or is not a Glympse user, you will need to create a link using the share dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the video review page, click share in the menu bar, then &lt;code&gt;generate share link&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will show you all the links for this file as well as the internal link that can be shared with Glympse users.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/share_link.png&#34; alt=&#34;Share Links&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To create a new link, click Generate link. This will allow you to set some options for the link.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/create_share.png&#34; alt=&#34;Share Links&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can add a password, an expiry date and select whether the file should be downloadable from this link.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/link_options.png&#34; alt=&#34;link options&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click generate and a new link will be created with the selected options.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/created_links.png&#34; alt=&#34;created Links&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can copy or delete any created links for the file.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upload Files</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/upload_and_manage_files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/upload_and_manage_files/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2&gt;Upload&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;upload&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#upload&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To upload a file, navigate to the review section of Glympse and click upload in the top right.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_upload.png&#34; alt=&#34;upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will take you to the upload form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every file you upload must belong to a production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Existing Production&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;existing-production&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#existing-production&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To upload to an existing production simply select it from the drop down menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next either select the file to upload or give it a title. If you leave the File Name field blank, by default it will use the filename of your selected file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select the file you&amp;rsquo;d like to upload by either dragging and dropping it into the upload box or clicking inside the box to bring the file select dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_upload_existing_file01.png&#34; alt=&#34;upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_upload_existing02.png&#34; alt=&#34;upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you have selected your file click upload and it will start uploading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New Production&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;new-production&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#new-production&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To upload a file to a new production, you will first need to create the Production. From the review upload page, click the blue + button.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_add_prod.png&#34; alt=&#34;upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will open the Add Production Modal. This is similar to adding a normal production, only here you don&amp;rsquo;t need to select a directory to scan for rushes or add a priority.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_add_prod2.png&#34; alt=&#34;upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you click submit, the production will be created and automatically selected on the upload form.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_production_added.png&#34; alt=&#34;upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select or drag and drop your file and click upload.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cancel upload&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;cancel-upload&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#cancel-upload&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you need to cancel an upload, you can stop and remove it by pressing the red X icon that shows when you hover your mouse over the progress bar.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/cancel_upload.png&#34; alt=&#34;Cancel upload&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Resume upload&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;resume-upload&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#resume-upload&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If for whatever reason the upload fails, you can resume the upload by submitting the same file with the same information and it will continue the upload from where it left off.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch and Review Files</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/watch_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/user_docs/review/watch_review/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;When you click on a file title from the review page, you will be taken the file viewing page. The viewing experience is similar to that of watching rushes, however with review files, multiple qualities are created. This allows for higher resolution viewing of a file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is also possible for anyone with download access to download the original file. Download access is given to all users in the production group or is specifically given when creating a download link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/review_file.png&#34; alt=&#34;Review File&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can play the video file and add markers as you watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Add Markers&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;add-markers&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#add-markers&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whilst the video is playing, you can add a marker by clicking in the box that says &amp;ldquo;Enter your notes here&amp;rdquo;. This will pause the video whilst you add your text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can change the type of marker by pressing the change marker button:
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/change_marker_type_btn.png&#34; alt=&#34;Change Marker&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will bring up a menu with the available marker types. Select the type you want to add and the marker button will change colour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/change_marker_type.png&#34; alt=&#34;marker menu&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you have entered your text in the box, click the save button or press &lt;code&gt;enter&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/blur_marker.png&#34; alt=&#34;blur marker&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The marker will be added to the right hand side of the video player.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/markers.png&#34; alt=&#34;Markers&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any markers added by you or others will appear here. MArkers will be added live if there are others reviewing the file at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the timecode of the marker will navigate the player to that timecode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is also possible to change the marker type after it has been added. The process is the same, click the change marker type button on the marker itself and select a new marker type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/change_marker_type_marker.png&#34; alt=&#34;Change Marker Type&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you added the marker, it&amp;rsquo;s also possible to change the marker text. It is also only possible for the person who added a marker to delete it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hover over the marker and the delete button will appear.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/delete_marker.png&#34; alt=&#34;delete marker&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can reply to any marker by pressing the reply button on a marker. This will allow you to add a reply to the markers.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/add_note.png&#34; alt=&#34;add note&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, only the person who adds the note can delete it. Unless the marker it&amp;rsquo;s applied to is deleted by someone else.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
